// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Where was COVID-19 first identified?",
    answer: "Wuhan, China",
    options: [
      "Beijing, China",
      "Xi An, China",
      "Guang Dong, China",
      "Wuhan, China"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which country had the highest number of cumulative cases?",
    answer: "America",
    options: [
      "France",
      "America",
      "Canada",
      "Singapore"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which country had the lowest number of cumulative cases?",
    answer: "New Zealand",
    options: [
      "New Zealand",
      "Singapore",
      "France",
      "India"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In Singapore, which category in F&B took the hardest toll during Circuit Breaker",
    answer: "Restaurants",
    options: [
      "Cafe",
      "Fast Food Outlets",
      "Food Caterers",
      "Restaurants"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What causes the decline on the index of department stores?",
    answer: "Non-Essential Business Closure",
    options: [
      "Non-Essential Business Closure",
      "Productivity Solution Grant for SMEs",
      "Circuit Breaker",
      "Ban Of Social Gathering"
    ]
  },
     {
     numb: 6,
     question: "When did MOH stop updating Linked and Unlinked Community Cases In Sinagpore?",
     answer: "19 August 2021",
     options: [
       "18 July 2021",
       "19 August 2020",
       "19 October 2020",
       "19 August 2021"
     ]
   },
   {
   numb: 7,
   question: "Which phase in Singapore has the most Covid-19 Cases?",
   answer: "Phase 2",
   options: [
     "Circuit Breaker",
     "Phase 3",
     "Phase 2",
     "Phase 2 (Heightened Alert)"
      ]
    },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the current phase in Singapore?",
    answer: "Stabilisation Stage",
    options: [
      "Stabilisation Stage",
      "Phase 3",
      "Circuit Breaker",
      "Preparatory Stage"
    ]
  },
     {
     numb: 8,
     question: "At which month of 2021 did the YOY% of visitor arrival increase the most?",
     answer: "April",
     options: [
       "March",
       "April",
       "May",
       "January"
     ]
   },
   {
   numb: 10,
   question: "What causes the spike in Average Length Of Stay in Singapore?",
   answer: "Quarrantine Order By Singapore Government",
   options: [
     "More visitor in Singapore",
     "Less visitors in Singapore",
     "People spend more time to travel in Singapore",
     "Quarrantine Order By Singapore Government"
      ]
    },
];
